axifile.com 2016-03-16

# FileRio : : Cloud File Storage

### Privacy Policy

This policy covers how we use your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information.  
Any personal information received will only be used to fill your order. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone. 

IP addresses of users  
FileRio : : Cloud File Storage can detect the IP address of your browser according to Internet-technology. This IP address is registered by our server especially for to help administer the website and track user's actions on the website. These details do not contain any personally identifiable information. 

E-mail  
Our server writes in the register of FileRio : : Cloud File Storage users’ e-mails only for their registration and calculation. FileRio : : Cloud File Storage will not lease, sell, or provide your personal information to any companies. 

Sharing of Information  
FileRio : : Cloud File Storage will only share information with 3rd parties if required to do so _by law_ , or if by doing so we can protect the FileRio : : Cloud File Storage website and/or it's users. If you do not wish for others to know your personal details (for example - name and email address), it is recommended that you do not apply for membership. 

Cookies use  
FileRio : : Cloud File Storage uses cookies for the users’ comfort in order to save the browser settings and to help make each user's visit easier and more interactive. FileRio : : Cloud File Storage does not any methods for tracking users (the so-called “spy” or “1x1” gif images and so on). 

Advertisements  
Advertisements located on our website can be posted by a third party – advertisement firms. These companies can use the information regarding your visits on these or other web pages (your name, address, e-mail, and phone number are excluded) to place an advertisement of wares and services that might be interesting to you. 

Links  
FileRio : : Cloud File Storage links to several other websites and does not control the content of any outside websites and can not be held accountable for their content. We also are not in control of the privacy policies of these sites and recommend that all members carefully read the privacy policies of other websites that collect personally identifiable information. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy  
If we make changes to this policy, we will let members know by posting mention of the changes on the homepage of this website. If we decide to use the personal details collected at membership signup (or during any other stage of a user's onsite activity) in any manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will let the user know via email. Users will be given a choice as to whether they want their information used in a different manner.
